(Sheldon:)-Sleep well, my friend.
-You too.
(Sheldon:)Let me just get one thing.
(Sheldon:)It's my backup emergency supply kit.
The living-room escape route
doesn't pass through here.
(Sheldon:)Now, good night.
(Sheldon:)And if there's an apocalypse,
good luck.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)Yes?
(Elizabeth:)-I saw your light on.
-Is everything all right?
(Elizabeth:)Yeah, I just couldn't sleep.
(Leonard:)Me neither.
(Leonard:)Look what I'm reading.
(Leonard:)It's you.
(Elizabeth:)-I thought you already read it.
-I did.
(Leonard:)But it's been a while, and I wanted
to sound smart over breakfast.
(Elizabeth:)Aw, you're smart.
Oh, good. I wasn't sure
it was coming across.
(Elizabeth:)What chapter are you on?
(Leonard:)Uh, six.
Ah. The extragalactic distance ladder.
(Elizabeth:)-Want to know a little secret?
-Sure.
(Elizabeth:)I wrote the section on the
Wilson-Bappu Effect completely naked.